clp.com.hk 2017-07-02

# CLP Privacy Policy Statement - CLP

### CLP Privacy Principles

As a responsible utility company, CLP is firmly committed to a set of business principles and ethics that help drive our company forward. One of these principles is respect for people and privacy and that begins with how we respect and protect the personal data we receive. To preserve the confidentiality of your personal data provided to us, we maintain the following data privacy principles:

  1. We only collect personal data that we believe to be relevant and required to conduct our business
  2. We will not disclose your personal data outside CLP unless we have your consent or are required by law
  3. We aim to keep your personal data accurate and up-to-date
  4. We maintain appropriate security systems designed to prevent unauthorized access to your personal data

### CLP Privacy Practices

 **Personal Data We Hold**

There are several broad categories of personal data held by CLP:

Customer records are kept for the purposes of providing services, facilities and goods to our customers; opening, maintaining and terminating accounts; processing payments and billing; responding and following up on customer inquiries, gaining an understanding of customers' energy needs, researching and developing products, conducting customer surveys and direct marketing activities.

Personnel records are kept for human resources administration purposes such as managing the recruitment, hiring, payroll, appraisal and termination of personnel of CLP.

Contractor records are kept for the purposes of engaging, managing, monitoring and appraising our professional relationships with contractors and their staff who provide services to CLP.

Other records that contain personal data held by CLP include records of our business partners, officers, shareholders, visitors and members of the public, and other operational and administrative records that contain personal data.

 **Transfer of Personal Data**

CLP will disclose personal data when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a law enforcement agency's request.

CLP may transfer your personal data to third parties such as employees, related companies, including subsidiaries and associated companies within the CLP Group, joint venture partners, agents, independent contractors, business associates and service providers, as necessary for any of the purposes stated above. Where personal data is provided to third party organizations, the personal data will only be transferred to such third parties that respects privacy and are under a duty of confidentiality to the CLP Group.

 **Accuracy of Personal Data**

CLP has certain procedures in place to maintain personal data at a reasonable level of accuracy, completeness and relevancy for the purpose for which the personal data is to be used. CLP aims to keep your data accurate and up-to-date. However, we rely on you to disclose all material information to us and to inform us of any errors or changes in such information. 

Individuals may amend their personal data, as appropriate, set out in "How You can Access or Correct Your Data" section below.

 **Retention of Personal Data**

CLP policy is to retain personal data for no longer than is required to fulfill the purpose (or any directly related purpose) for which the data was to be used, subject to legal, statutory and regulatory requirements mandating the retention of data.

 **Security of Personal Data**

CLP has put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help protect personal data against unauthorized or accidental access, processing, erasure or other use.

 **Direct Marketing Activities**

If you prefer for your personal data not to be used for the purposes of direct marketing activities, please send an email, along with your name to our Data Protection Officer at [csd@clp.com.hk](mailto:csd@clp.com.hk) notifying us that you do not wish your personal data to be used for such purposes.

 **Personal Data Collected Through This Website**

We may collect personal data through your use of this website such as name, gender, age, telephone number and email address. Certain information about your computer may also be collected when you visit this website, such as the type of the Internet browser and operating system you are using and the domain name of your Internet service provider. You are not required by law to provide your personal data. However, CLP may not be able to provide you with the services, facilities and goods you may require unless you provide the personal data sought from you.

 **Use of Personal Data Collected Through This Website**

The CLP Group uses the personal data collected through this website primarily for supplying to you the services, facilities and goods you require; to respond to your inquiries; to gain an understanding of your energy needs; to perform statistical analysis, analysis of website usage or customer requirements; direct marketing activities; and to notify you of any changes to this website or our services which may affect you.

 **Cookies**

Some of the web pages on this website contain "cookies" to enhance your experience of this website. Cookies are text files placed in your computer's Internet browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not provide your e-mail address or other personal data. The CLP Group only obtains this information when you choose to provide it to the website. However, once you choose to furnish the website with your personal data, such data may be linked to data stored in the cookie. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you would prefer, you can set your browser to disable cookies or inform you when they are set. But if you do, certain functionalities of this website may not be available to you.

 **Access and Correction of Your Data**

You can update or correct your personal data by sending an email request to our Data Protection Officer at [csd@clp.com.hk](mailto:csd@clp.com.hk). The CLP Group will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections to your personal data to protect your privacy and identity.

 **How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about the CLP Group's Privacy Policy Statement including our data practices for this website or its usage, you may contact our Data Protection Officer at [csd@clp.com.hk](mailto:csd@clp.com.hk) or write to the following address:

CLP Power Hong Kong Limited  
Data Protection Officer  
13/F, 6 On Lai Street  
Shatin  
NT  
Hong Kong

Unless specified otherwise, references in this site to "CLP" and the "CLP Group" shall mean CLP Holdings Limited, its subsidiaries and affiliates in Hong Kong.

We may change this Privacy Policy Statement from time to time. We encourage you to check this Privacy Policy Statement occasionally to ensure that you are aware of the most recent version.

Personal Information Collection Statement
